propertytribes.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy notice

This privacy notice lets you know what happens to any personal data that you give to Property Tribes Ltd.

This privacy notice applies to personal information processed by Property Tribes Ltd.

**1\. Property Tribes Ltd and our Data Protection Officer**

We are Property Tribes Ltd, 69, High Street, London, N14 6LD, and a data controller of your personal data. The company registration number is 07875701.

We have a dedicated data protection officer (“DPO”). You can contact the DPO using the email nick-tadd@mac.com.

**2\. What kinds of personal information about you does Property Tribes process?**

Personal information that we’ll process in connection with your membership of our site, if relevant, includes:

Personal and contact details, such as title, full name, and email address, although some users use a different name to their own.

Your date of birth, gender and/or age - should you choose to input that information.

When you visit our site we may automatically log your IP address, a unique identifier for your computer or other access device. This information is not used in any way other to identify trolling activity, cyber attacks, or people holding multiple profiles.

**3\. How does Property Tribes use this data to communicate with you?**

We use this data for communication with you when sending you our bi-weekly emailer newsletter (if you opted in), including history of those communications, whether you open them or click on links.

You can withdraw your consent at any time by unsubscribing or contacting the Data Protection Officer.

**4\. What is the source of your personal information?**

We collect personal information from you directly.

**5\. What does Property Tribes use your personal information for?**

As per no. 2, we use your email address to send you our newsletter, if you opted in, or to send you notifications that threads have been up-dated, if you opted in.

You can manually opt out of these if you no longer which to receive them, and can contact us for help if you require assistance.

**6\. Do you share my personal information?**

Property Tribes respects your privacy and does not share your personal data with any third party or any of our commercial partners.

**7\. What are your rights under data protection laws?**

Here is a list of the rights that all individuals have under data protection laws. They don’t apply in all circumstances. If you wish to use any of them, we’ll explain at that time if they are engaged or not. The right of data portability is only relevant from May 2018.

The right to be informed about the processing of your personal information

The right to have your personal information corrected if it is inaccurate and to have incomplete personal information completed

The right to object to processing of your personal information

The right to restrict processing of your personal information

The right to have your personal information erased (the “right to be forgotten”)

The right to request access to your personal information and to obtain information about how we process it The right to move, copy or transfer your personal information (“data portability”)

**8\. Google “push” notifications**

You may have elected to receive notifications of new threads being added to Property Tribes by opting in to our google push notifications service. You would have pressed the “Allow” button when offered this service. If you have done this, you will see a small opaque bell icon on the bottom right of your screen when visiting Property Tribes.

Property Tribes does not hold any personal data for opting in to this service and cannot identify you in any way.

Should you wish to no longer receive these notifications, simply press the small “bell” icon bottom right of your screen when on Property Tribes, and the notifications will be disabled.

**9\. Any questions?**

Please contact the Data Protection Office by [e-mail](mailto:nicktadd@badmail.mac.com) or use the Contact Us information.
